{
    "id": "26d5453624a34a248fe2a4fd9543224a",
    "title": "Fill In The Blanks | General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Tell me if you ……………………….. any help.",
            "description": "The simple present is used in situations like these. ",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "will need",
                "would need"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d86612135b754ba382f1e62e821e451e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The first time I ………………………… him was at university.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to say when something happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "had met",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "baca698369374b55b3fbd79956f28ebe"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the garage ……………………….. they used to work.",
            "description": "Where means in which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "864cfcb864ad4c3b9be3c0b766529c97"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………. a terrible experience yesterday.",
            "description": "Had is the past simple form of have. ",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "have",
                "have had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30cbe96b1b3e42968a8f645211021a67"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is my biggest regret …………………………",
            "description": "Yet shows time up to now. ",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "still",
                "already"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "079d1f10ce81465ebff9548ad2e7e861"
        },
        {
            "question": "The valley ………………………….. quiet and beautiful in the morning.",
            "description": "Lay is the past simple form of lie. ",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "lays",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1886dfaaa8945cf80a2d4202281846a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of us ……………………………. the world differently.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "sees",
                "see",
                "seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5a5c017b1d06497e966ded92bd92dab8"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… his illness, he could not write the exam.",
            "description": "Owing to and due to both mean because of.",
            "answers": [
                "Owing to",
                "Due to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2de7e2d716534a4c84b9827aaf888f3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The summer term ………………………… on April 12th.",
            "description": "The simple present is more appropriate here. It is used to talk about predetermined actions that are part of a time table. ",
            "answers": [
                "will start",
                "is starting",
                "starts"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "235ff484bb67457a9b0903901768b9fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will pay you back when I ………………………… a job.",
            "description": "When both clauses refer to the future, a simple present is used after when.",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "get",
                "would get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94b041d0dc624ac5b30c5502bb5a8d49"
        },
        {
            "question": "I promise I …………………………… in the evening.",
            "description": "Simple future is used to express this idea. ",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "will come",
                "would come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e09a96f388d9480d8c95b31fd4d6a2bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I stayed in bed all day ……………………………. going to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead",
                "instead of",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa405a21089f40afb7e4f338d1632de8"
        }
    ]
}